Guide to the Tuol Sleng confessions and photographs, 1991-1993
Tuol Sleng confessions and photographs, 1991-1993
- Series II: Confessions I-N
  - Names: L
    - Leang Chanthen, 11/1976/ (Reel 62, Frame 1)
      30/11/1976; 2/11/1976; 23/10/1976
    - Leang Hong, N/A (Reel 61, Frame 21)
      Dates of Confessions: 1/6/1978
    - Leang Nan, 23/3/1977 (Reel 69, Frame 13)
    - Leang Ngov, 20/5/1976 (Reel 68, Frame 33)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/2/1976
    - Leang Sim Horn, N/A (Reel 61, Frame 24)
    - Leap, N/A (Reel 61, Frame 20)
      Dates of Confessions: 11/10/1976
    - Leap Prel, 8/17/1978 (Reel 68, Frame 18)
    - Leat Lean Hurr, 16/7/1977 (Reel 69, Frame 5)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/8/1976; 20/8/1977; 22/8/1977
    - Leav Huor Se, 1/1976 (Reel 68, Frame 10)
    - Leav Soth Sophorntha, 13/12/1975 (Reel 61, Frame 22)
      Dates of Confessions: 7/12/1975
    - Lek Hay, N/A (Reel 67, Frame 19)
      Dates of Confessions: 31/8/1976; 2/9/1976; 4/9/1976; 5/9/1976; 8/9/1976; 7/9/1976(2); 9/9/1976; 11/9/1976; 15/9/1976; 18/9/1976; 19/9/1976; 17/9/1976(2)
    - Lem Tith, N/A (Reel 69, Frame 28)
    - Leng Eang, N/A (Reel 69, Frame 4)
    - Leng Khorn, 2/2/1978 (Reel 69, Frame 26)
    - Leng Nhuon, N/A (Reel 61, Frame 28)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/6/1978; 14/10/1978
    - Leng Peng, N/A (Reel 68, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 11/8/1977
    - Leng Proeurn, 22/9/1978 (Reel 68, Frame 6)
    - Leng Py, N/A (Reel 67, Frame 3)
    - Leng Sean, 2/1978 (Reel 68, Frame 29)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/2/1978; 15/3/1978
    - Leng Sim Hak, 18/12/1977 (Reel 61, Frame 25)
      Dates of Confessions: 1/2/1978; 17/2/1978(2); 25/1/1978(2); 21/1/1978; 17/1/1978; 6/1/1978
    - Leng Vang, 16/8/1977 (Reel 61, Frame 27)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/9/1977; 3/9/1977; 7/9/1977; 13/9/1977; 1 section undated
    - Leung Phoeurng, 1/12/1978 (Reel 68, Frame 32)
    - Lev Leap, N/A (Reel 61, Frame 10)
    - Ley Chhoy, 26/6/1978 (Reel 67, Frame 22)
      Dates of Confessions: 1/6/1978; 6/7/1978
    - Ley Phorth, 7/7/1977 (Reel 61, Frame 23)
      Dates of Confessions: 15/4/1977; 27/8/1977`
    - Lim Be, N/A (Reel 69, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 11/8/1992
    - Lim Chhay Hong, 8/9/1977 (Reel 66, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 24/2/1978; 6/3/1978; 1 section undated
    - Lim Hak, 16/3/1978 (Reel 68, Frame 19)
    - Lim Kim, 15/11/1977 (Reel 67, Frame 4)
    - Lim Kimary, 13/2/1976 (Reel 66, Frame 16)
    - Lim Lai, N/A (Reel 69, Frame 27)
    - Lim Lay, 1/1976 (Reel 62, Frame 11)
    - Lim Lun, 1/7/1976 (Reel 62, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 20/7/1976; 18/7/1976; 1/11/1976; 14/7/1976; 22/7/1976; 23/7/1976; 24/7/1976; 19/7/1976; 24/7/1976; 18/7/1976; 16/7/1976; 23/7/1976; 23/7/1976; 25/7/1976
      19/7/1976; 14/7/1976; 25/7/1976; 24/7/1976; 22/7/1976; 17/7/1976; 17/7/1976
      15/7/1976; 15/7/1976; 15/7/1976; 12/11/1976; 9/11/1976; 18/7/1976; 25/7/1976
    - Lim Ly, 31/7/1978 (Reel 69, Frame 20)
    - Lim Meng, 9/5/1978 (Reel 66, Frame 8)
    - Lim Nan, 25/7/1978 (Reel 62, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/7/1978
    - Lim Nhim, 9/10/1976 (Reel 66, Frame 20)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/10/1976; 28/10/1976; 31/10/1976; 8/11/1976; 9/11/1976; 10/11/1976; 13/11/1976(2); 17/11/1976; 18/11/1976; 20/11/1976; 21/11/1976; 24/11/1976
      26/11/1976; 29/11/1976; 7/12/1976; 4/12/1976; 22/1/1977; 2 sections undated
    - Lim Ork, N/A (Reel 68, Frame 4)
    - Lim Pav, 18/3/1978 (Reel 69, Frame 11)
    - Lim Puoy Leng, N/A (Reel 62, Frame 8)
      Dates of Confessions: 26/1/1978; 3/2/1978
    - Lim Siv, N/A (Reel 67, Frame 18)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/6/1977; 10/9/1977
    - Lim Soeurng, N/A (Reel 65, Frame 8)
      Dates of Confessions: 27/9/1976; 28/9/1976; 30/9/1976; 2/10/1976; 3/10/1976; 5/10/1976; 7/10/1976; 11/10/1976(2); 12/10/1976; 9/10/1976; 23/10/1976; 7/10/1976; 11/10/1976(2)
      12/10/1976; 9/10/1976; 23/10/1976; 24/10/1976; 25/10/1976; 19/10/1976(3)
      26/10/1976; 27/10/1976; 30/10/1976; 7/12/1976; 5/1/1977; 9/1/1976; 5 sections undated
    - Lim Sok, N/A (Reel 62, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 22/12/1976; 16/12/1976; 7/12/1976; 7/12/1976; 23/11/1976; 27/11/1976; 25/11/1976; 16/11/1976; 24/12/1976; 12/1/1977; 2 sections undated
    - Lim Som, 28/3/1978 (Reel 67, Frame 33)
      Dates of Confessions: 30/8/1978
    - Lim Sun Bac Lim, 6/1/1978 (Reel 65, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/1/1978; 27/2/1978; 1 section undated
    - Lim Teng, 11/1977 (Reel 67, Frame 31)
    - Lim Than, 5/3/1978 (Reel 67, Frame 23)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/3/1978; 2 sections undated
    - Lim Tork, 1/10/1975 (Reel 69, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 22/10/1975
    - Lim Yet, 16/1/1978 (Reel 68, Frame 17)
    - Liu Trung Tinh, 10/11/1978 (Reel 186, Frame 6)
    - Liv Chhem, 23/10/1978 (Reel 67, Frame 27)
      Dates of Confessions: 7/11/1978
    - Lo Vuth, N/A (Reel 69, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/9/1977
    - Lo You, 20/5/1976 (Reel 69, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/9/1976
    - Loch Pot, N/A (Reel 69, Frame 19)
      Dates of Confessions: 10/12/1976; 14/12/1976; 15/12/1976; 16/12/1976; 19/12/1976; 20/12/1976; 21/12/1976; 3/1/1976; 4/1/1976; 6/1/1976; 7/1/1976; 8/1/1977; 13/1/1977
      12/1/1977; 6/1/1977
    - Loch Srong, 2 6 77 (Reel 66, Frame 4)
    - Loch Tong, 28/4/1977 (Reel 68, Frame 12)
    - Loek Choeun, 5/10/1977 (Reel 69, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 21/3/1978; 6/7/1978; 7/2/1978; 7/8/1978
    - Loek Hem, N/A (Reel 61, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/5/1977
    - Loek Soeut, 26/6/1978 (Reel 68, Frame 31)
    - Loem Lorm, 26/7/1977 (Reel 62, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/8/1977; 22/8/1977
    - Loem Voek Tung, 3/1978 (Reel 186, Frame 76)
    - Loeng Seng, 5/1977 (Reel 62, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/10/1977; 8/7/1977; 14/9/1977; 15/9/1977
    - Loeng Soeurk, 5/8/1977 (Reel 67, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 24/8/1977; 1/9/1978
    - Loeng Teav, 30/3/1977 (Reel 67, Frame 20)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/4/1977; 3 sections undated
    - Loeng Van, N/A (Reel 62, Frame 4)
    - Loeurn Chhom, N/A (Reel 69, Frame 8)
    - Loeurn Soeurn, 7/1977 (Reel 69, Frame 21)
      Dates of Confessions: 6/8/1977; 12/9/1977; 16/9/1977; 22/9/1977; 9/2/1978
    - Loeurng Buth, N/A (Reel 61, Frame 26)
    - Loeurng Ly, 6/4/1977 (Reel 64, Frame 10)
      Dates of Confessions: 24/8/1977; 19/11/1977; 20/11/1977; 21/11/1977; 22/11/1977; 28/11/1977; 23/11/1977; 24/11/1977
    - Loeurng Ly, 6/4/1977 (Reel 67, Frame 25)
    - Lok Born, 6/10/1977 (Reel 67, Frame 8)
    - Lok Bun, 24/3/1976 (Reel 65, Frame 3)
    - Lok Chay, 12/2/1978 (Reel 68, Frame 16)
    - Lom Songoeurn, 11/1/1977 (Reel 67, Frame 1)
    - Lomm (Lamm) Thi Thu, 10/9/1978 (Reel 186, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/10/1978; 9/10/1978
    - Lon, N/A (Reel 67, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 8/2/1977
    - Long Bas, 9/12/1977 (Reel 66, Frame 10)
    - Long Bun Kim, N/A (Reel 64, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 24/4/1977; 25/4/1977; 26/4/1977; 27/4/1977; 28/4/1977; 29/4/1977; 30/4/1977; 17/5/1977
    - Long Chamrourn, N/A (Reel 64, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/10/1977; 2/8/1977; 9/10/1977
    - Long Chhea, 27/10/1977 (Reel 67, Frame 5)
    - Long Chhin, N/A (Reel 66, Frame 24)
    - Long Chhoeut, N/A (Reel 65, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/3/1977; 17/3/1977; 18/3/1977; 19/3/1977; 20/3/1977; 23/3/1977; 26/3/1977; 23/3/1977; 24/3/1977; 25/3/1977; 26/3/1977
      27/3/1977; 28/3/1977; 29/3/1977; 1 section undated
    - Long Heng, 22/9/1975 (Reel 67, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 29/9/1975
    - Long La, N/A (Reel 65, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/3/1977; 20/3/1977; 21/3/1977; 1 section undated
    - Long Leng, N/A (Reel 68, Frame 8)
      Dates of Confessions: 31/3/1977; 16/10/1977; 17/9/1977; 25/5/1977
    - Long Leng Chhoeng, 12/10/1976 (Reel 62, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/11/1976; 25/11/1976
    - Long Lorn, 18/7/1976 (Reel 65, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 28/7/1975; 26/12/1975
    - Long Luch, N/A (Reel 68, Frame 2)
    - Long Lum Ham, N/A (Reel 66, Frame 17)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/5/1977; 10/5/1977; 11/5/1977; 12/5/1977
    - Long Mamirith, 31/12/1977 (Reel 65, Frame 5)
      Dates of Confessions: 7/2/1978; 23/4/1978; 25/4/1978
    - Long Muy, 12/7/1977 (Reel 66, Frame 18)
      Dates of Confessions: 29/8/1977; 1/8/1977
    - Long Phan, N/A (Reel 64, Frame 17)
      Dates of Confessions: 27/9/1976(2); 25/9/1976; 26/9/1976(2); 28/9/1976(2); 29/9/1976(2); 25/9/1976
    - Long Rin, 4/7/1977 (Reel 64, Frame 16)
    - Long Sam Oeur, N/A (Reel 64, Frame 8)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/3/1977(3); 17/2/1977; 25/2/1977; 17/3/1977; 16/3/1977; 22/4/1977; 30/6/1977; 7/3/1977; 2 sections undated
    - Long Sam Oeur, N/A (Reel 68, Frame 25)
    - Long Sam Phal, 24/3/1978 (Reel 65, Frame 4)
    - Long Sama, N/A (Reel 66, Frame 13)
    - Long Saran, 12/1978 (Reel 64, Frame 18)
    - Long Seng, N/A (Reel 66, Frame 3)
    - Long Thach, 17/7/1978 (Reel 68, Frame 21)
    - Long Tik, N/A (Reel 67, Frame 26)
    - Long Yan, 15/5/1977 (Reel 66, Frame 5)
    - Lonh Chrek, 25/6/1976 (Reel 68, Frame 28)
      Dates of Confessions: 19/8/1976; 19/8/1976
    - Lonh Juan, N/A (Reel 66, Frame 7)
    - Lonh Noeurn, N/A (Reel 67, Frame 30)
    - Lor Eang Kong (Lep Eang Kang), 6/7/1978 (Reel 187, Frame 18)
    - Lor Ing, N/A (Reel 67, Frame 35)
    - Lor Koeun, 2/1977 (Reel 69, Frame 24)
      Dates of Confessions: 7/2/1977; 10/2/1977; 14/2/1977
    - Lor Sras, N/A (Reel 64, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/8/1976; 23/8/1976; 24/8/1976; 6/7/1976
    - Lor Sreng, 18/12/1976 (Reel 66, Frame 22)
    - Lork Yoeut, N/A (Reel 66, Frame 6)
    - Lors Bun Leang, N/A (Reel 67, Frame 28)
      Dates of Confessions: 7/9/1976
    - Lors Oeurn, 12/17/1975 (Reel 64, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/2/1975
    - Lors Yan, 8/3/1977 (Reel 68, Frame 26)
    - Lot, 3/2/1978 (Reel 68, Frame 23)
    - Lot Sean, 8/1977 (Reel 68, Frame 27)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/8/1977; 15/11/1977
    - Lot Sophon, 12/6/1978 (Reel 67, Frame 34)
    - Lou Ly, 22/1/1977 (Reel 68, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 6/2/1977; 5/2/1977(2); 4/2/1977; 5/1/1977; 6/1/1977; 8/2/1977
    - Louk Lam, 6/8/1977 (Reel 66, Frame 15)
    - Lov Hy, 20/8/1975 (Reel 67, Frame 2)
    - Loy Srun, 12/8/1977 (Reel 69, Frame 25)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/8/1977
    - Luch Phal, 9/1977 (Reel 68, Frame 15)
    - Luk Thai, N/A (Reel 64, Frame 2)
    - Lun Chun, 21/8/1977 (Reel 69, Frame 29)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/9/1977
    - Lun Hok, 2/10/1975 (Reel 62, Frame 7)
    - Lun In, 9/71 (Reel 69, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 20/10/1977
    - Lun Khem, N/A (Reel 66, Frame 27)
    - Lun Ray, N/A (Reel 62, Frame 10)
    - Lun Tean, 8/4/1977 (Reel 66, Frame 23)
      Dates of Confessions: 22/8/1977; 10/8/1977
    - Luom Sam (Som) Boun, N/A (Reel 185, Frame 32)
      Age: 67
    - Luon Lom, N/A (Reel 62, Frame 5)
    - Luon Sao, 5/7/1978 (Reel 67, Frame 32)
    - Luon Then, N/A (Reel 68, Frame 5)
    - Luong Thavarak, 12/11/1977 (Reel 66, Frame 25)
    - Luy Heng, 3/2/1978 (Reel 66, Frame 26)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/4/1978; 5/2/1978
    - Luy Loeurn, 6/1977 (Reel 66, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 27/9/1977; 20/8/1977
    - Luy Ny, N/A (Reel 68, Frame 1)
    - Ly Ang, 12/10/1976 (Reel 63, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 26/10/1976(3); 27/10/1976(6); 28/10/1976(7); 29/10/1976(9); 3o/10/1976(8); 2/11/1976(2); 3/11/1976(3); 4/11/1976(4); 8/11/1976(3); 9/11/1976(3)
      10/11/1976(3); 11/11/1976(5); 12/11/1976(4); 13/11/1976(3); 14/11/1976(2)
      15/11/1976(1); 15/11/1976(3); 23/11/1976; 24/11/1976(2); 21/11/1976(2)
    - Ly Ang, N/A (Reel 68, Frame 20)
    - Ly Bun Chheang, N/A (Reel 64, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 19/10/1976; 20/10/1976; 21/10/1976; 17/10/1976; 18/10/1976; 13/10/1976; 16/10/1976(2); 12/10/1976(2); 9/10/1976; 21/10/1976
    - Ly Bun Soeurn, 3/3/1976 (Reel 64, Frame 3)
    - Ly Choeu Kheang, 19/3/1978 (Reel 67, Frame 17)
      Dates of Confessions: 24/3/1978
    - Ly Davy, 8/1977 (Reel 64, Frame 6)
    - Ly Hak, 26/2/1977 (Reel 67, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 1/5/1977; 13/6/1977
    - Ly Hay, 10/11/1976 (Reel 63, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/12/1976; 3/1/1977; 27/12/1976; 5/1/1976; 21/12/1976; 24/11/1976; 7/12/1976; 2/12/1976
    - Ly Heng, N/A (Reel 66, Frame 28)
    - Ly Kheav, N/A (Reel 68, Frame 13)
    - Ly Len, 9/12/1977 (Reel 64, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 1/3/1978
    - Ly Mech, N/A (Reel 69, Frame 10)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/8/1976
    - Ly Phen, N/A (Reel 64, Frame 5)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/7/1976; 18/9/1976; 20/9/1976; 27/9/1976; 19/9/1976; 24/7/1976; 15/7/1976; 22/7/1976; 20/9/1976; 21/9/1976; 31/7/1976; 7/7/1976
      20/6/1976; 18/7/1976; 31/7/1976; 5/8/1976
    - Ly Rasy, N/A (Reel 67, Frame 16)
    - Ly Se, N/A (Reel 64, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 1/5/1977; 29/4/1977; 20/5/1977; 21/4/1977
    - Ly Suk Pheng, N/A (Reel 69, Frame 18)
    - Ly Tha, N/A (Reel 68, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 30/6/1977
    - Ly Vaiy, N/A (Reel 64, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 6/1976; 7/6/1976(2); 16/6/1976; 21/7/1976; 20/6/1976; 13/6/1976; 17/6/1976; 9/6/1976(2); 3/6/1976; 18/6/1976(3); 27/6/1976; 22/6/1976
      8/6/1976(2); 9/9/1976; 22/6/1976; 4/6/1976; 29/5/1976; 7/1976; 6/1976
    - Ly Van Suy, N/A (Reel 186, Frame 111)
    - Ly York Boy, 28/8/1977 (Reel 62, Frame 12)
    - Ly Yum, N/A (Reel 69, Frame 23)
  - Names: M
    - Ma Meng Kheang, 10/3/1977 (Reel 69, Frame 30)
      Dates of Confessions: 18/3/1977; 4/4/1977; 7/4/1977; 1 section undated
    - Ma Rayom ( India ), 11/4/1976 (Reel 185, Frame 16)
      Age: 63
    - Ma Saroeun, N/A (Reel 79, Frame 14)
    - Ma Suos, N/A (Reel 69, Frame 31)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/10/1976; 30/9/1976; 8/10/1976(2); 10/10/1976; 13/10/1976(6); 7/10/1976; 9/10/1976(2); 5/10/1976; 25/10/1976; 6/10/1976; 29/10/1976(2); 27/9/1976
      3/10/1976; 4/10/1976
    - Ma Tong, 4/3/1977 (Reel 80, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/6/1977; 14/6/1977
    - Ma Um, N/A (Reel 77, Frame 17)
    - Mab Chhoeuy, 30/4/1978 (Reel 69, Frame 32)
    - Mach, N/A (Reel 79, Frame 18)
    - Maing Chhan, N/A (Reel 75, Frame 21)
      Dates of Confessions: 23/3/1977(3); 12/3/1977; 13/3/1977; 14/3/1977; 19/3/1977; 15/3/1977; 17/3/1977; 21/3/1977; 18/3/1977
    - Mak Chhorn, 4/11/2007 (Reel 70, Frame 3)
    - Mak Heang, 1/3/1977 (Reel 71, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/5/1977; 26/5/1977; 28/5/1977; 29/5/1977; 30/5/1977; 31/5/1977; 1/6/1977; 2/6/1977; 3/6/1977; 5/6/1977
    - Mak Kim Sam On, N/A (Reel 79, Frame 3)
    - Mak Laum, N/A (Reel 77, Frame 7)
    - Mak Loeng, N/A (Reel 75, Frame 18)
    - Mak Mean, N/A (Reel 70, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/10/1976; 2/10/1976(2); 1/10/ 76; 20/9/1976(2); 18/10/1976; 16/10/1976; 19/10/1976(2); 12/10/1976; 24/10/1976; 22/10/1976; 13/10/1976
      10/10/1976(2); 6/10/1976; 11/10/1976; 1/11/1976
    - Mak Mok, N/A (Reel 79, Frame 25)
    - Mak Phain, 31/12/1976 (Reel 70, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 28/1/1977; 6/2/1977; 3 sections undated
    - Mak Ran, 26/10/1978 (Reel 70, Frame 18)
      Dates of Confessions: 6/11/1978; 13/11/1978
    - Mak Sam Ol, 1/1/1978 (Reel 80, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/1/1978; 9/1/1978; 23/1/1978
    - Mak Somith, N/A (Reel 74, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 24/1/1977/ 25/1/1977
    - Mak Sorn, 13/8/1978 (Reel 78, Frame 4)
    - Mak Sorth, 3/11/1978 (Reel 79, Frame 31)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/11/1978
    - Mak Theng, N/A (Reel 78, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/2/1977(2); 2 sections undated
    - Mak Yi Hoeurng, N/A (Reel 75, Frame 3)
    - Mam Bol, 24/1/1978 (Reel 80, Frame 28)
    - Mam Doeung, N/A (Reel 79, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 18/1/1977; 26/1/1977
    - Mam Doeurn, 15/6/1978 (Reel 80, Frame 33)
      Dates of Confessions: 15/7/1978
    - Mam Eang, N/A (Reel 71, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 9 10/1977; 15/9/1977
    - Mam Keng, N/A (Reel 76, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/11/1976; 7 sections undated
    - Mam Khoeun, N/A (Reel 78, Frame 22)
    - Mam Moeun, 27/7/1978 (Reel 80, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/8/1978
    - Mam Roeup, 2/4/1978 (Reel 70, Frame 8)
    - Mam Saman, N/A (Reel 75, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 28/4/1978
    - Mam Sothun, 29/8/1975 (Reel 75, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 22/8/92
    - Mam Visal, N/A (Reel 70, Frame 5)
      Dates of Confessions: 21/6/1976; 5/7/1976; 1/8/1976; 20/7/1976(3); 6/7/1976(2); 31/7/1976(2); 14/8/1976; 17/7/1976; 18/7/1976(2); 13/7/1976; 15 sections undated
    - Man Lors, 4/2/1978 (Reel 78, Frame 16)
    - Man Math, 10/1975 (Reel 70, Frame 11)
    - Man Moeurn, 9/1977 (Reel 70, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 27/9/1977; 2/10/1977; 3/10/1977; 5/9/1977; 18/9/1977; 16/10/1977
    - Man Moeuy, 1/1978 (Reel 78, Frame 24)
    - Man Sambo, 4/8/1976 (Reel 70, Frame 10)
      Dates of Confessions: 15/8/1976; 16/8/1976; 17/8/1976 21/8/1976; 18/8/1976; 21/8/1976; 22/8/1976(2); 23/8/1976(3); 25/8/1976(3); 26/8/1976(3)
      3/9/1976(2); 26/5/1976(5); 27/8/1976(5); 29/8/1976; 30/8/1976; 31/8/1976(2)
      1/9/1976(2); 2/9/1976; 5/9/1976(3); 4/9/1976(2); 7/9/1976; 10/9/1976
      12/9/1976; 2 sections undated
    - Man Sarun, N/A (Reel 76, Frame 21)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/10/1976(2); 3 sections undated
    - Man Sim, N/A (Reel 78, Frame 28)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/1/1977; 21/1/1977
    - Manauot Chay (Manaot Chuy ) Chem Sai, 21/12/1975 (Reel 185, Frame 36)
    - Mang Lame, 23/7/1978 (Reel 76, Frame 20)
      Dates of Confessions: 20/8/1978(3)
    - Mang Pum, 15/6/1978 (Reel 77, Frame 20)
    - Manh Hok Chhoeun, N/A (Reel 80, Frame 7)
    - Mann Muy, N/A (Reel 73, Frame 16)
      Dates of Confessions: 28/7/1977
    - Mann Van Thay, 4/10/1975 (Reel 76, Frame 13)
    - Mao Chan Phal, 5/10/1975 (Reel 79, Frame 5)
    - Mao Chhin, 9/12/1977 (Reel 71, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 6/1/1978; 17/12/1977
    - Mao Chhum, 11/7/1978 (Reel 79, Frame 29)
      Dates of Confessions: 31/8/1978; 19/9/1978
    - Mao Choeun, 17/9/1977 (Reel 76, Frame 8)
      Dates of Confessions: 24/9/1977; 25/9/1977; 27/9/1977;(3); 28/9/1977; 15/10/1977; 28/10/1977
    - Mao Douk, N/A (Reel 74, Frame 25)
      Dates of Confessions: 29/3/1977; 1/6/1977
    - Mao Dul, 2/10/1978 (Reel 78, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 10/10/1976; 13/10/1976; 18/10/1976; 27/10/1976; 11/11/1976; 19/10/1976(2); 10/1/1977; 17/11/1976; 8/1/1977; 6/1/1977; 4/1/1977(3)
      20/1/1977; 24/11/1976; 6/12/1976; 11/12/1976; 11/12/1976; 12/12/1976
      11/10/1976; 5 sections undated
    - Mao Heang, 27/8/1978 (Reel 78, Frame 20)
    - Mao Hok, 13/4/1977 (Reel 79, Frame 16)
    - Mao Khem Noeun, 5/4/1977 (Reel 75, Frame 16)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/4/1977; 16/4/1977; 24/4/1977; 23/4/1977; 27/4/1977; 3/5/1977; 6/5/1977(2)
    - Mao Khin, N/A (Reel 78, Frame 18)
    - Mao Khmek, 16/3/1977 (Reel 75, Frame 6)
    - Mao Kim Srea, 7/5/1977 (Reel 71, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/7/1977; 17/7/1977
    - Mao Lan, 25/1/1977 (Reel 79, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/2/1977
    - Mao Met, 30/11/1978 (Reel 80, Frame 35)
      Dates of Confessions: 20/12/1978
    - Mao Moran, 6/10/1975 (Reel 79, Frame 33)
    - Mao My, 18/12/1975 (Reel 75, Frame 9)
    - Mao Nat, N/A (Reel 78, Frame 9)
    - Mao Neou, N/A (Reel 74, Frame 13)
    - Mao Phan, 1/4/1978 (Reel 75, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 10/4/1978; 10/6/1978
    - Mao Phen, N/A (Reel 74, Frame 22)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/2/1977; 19/2/1977; 3/3/1977
    - Mao Poul, 8/9/1978 (Reel 79, Frame 30)
      Dates of Confessions: 22/9/1978
    - Mao Run, 11/3/1977 (Reel 79, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/3/1977; 8/5/1977; 13/7/1977
    - Mao Sakhom, 20/3/1977 (Reel 71, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 10/5/1977; 11/5/1977; 12/5/1977; 13/5/1977
    - Mao San, 22/9/1977 (Reel 76, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 17/11/1977
    - Mao Sarith, N/A (Reel 80, Frame 20)
    - Mao Saroeurn, 11/8/1977 (Reel 79, Frame 32)
      Dates of Confessions: 29/8/1977; 13/10/1977; 18/8/1977
    - Mao Sem, 15/10/1977 (Reel 77, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/12/1977
    - Mao Sem, N/A (Reel 79, Frame 12)
    - Mao Seng, 3/1977 (Reel 80, Frame 14)
    - Mao Sokha, 31/12/1976 (Reel 74, Frame 21)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/1/1977; 6/2/1977(2); 7/2/1977; 16/3/1977; 7/4/1977; 2 sections undated
    - Mao Sophany, 12/1/1976 (Reel 77, Frame 24)
    - Mao Than, 7/1977/ (Reel 79, Frame 7)
    - Mao Yin, 15/9/1977 (Reel 77, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/12/1977
    - Map Rat ( Revolutionary Name ), N/A (Reel 73, Frame 26)
    - Map Yun, 3/11/1978 (Reel 70, Frame 9)
    - Mars Em, 1/2/1978 (Reel 79, Frame 11)
    - Math Less, 27/1/1978 (Reel 80, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/2/1978(2); 3/3/1978
    - Mauk Moth, N/A (Reel 77, Frame 10)
    - Maung Vuth, N/A (Reel 79, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 23/4/1978; 21/6/1978
    - Maunh Say, 8/2/1977 (Reel 70, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 19/2/1977; 20/2/1977; 21/2/1977; 22/2/1977; 23/2/1977; 24/2/1977; 25/2/1977; 26/2/1977; 28/2/1977; 27/2/1977; 1/3/1977; 2/3/1977; 4/3/1977
      5/4/1977; 6/4/1977; 7/3/1977; 8/3/1977; 9/3/1977; 11/3/1977; 12/3/1977
      13/3/1977; 14/3/1977; 15/3/1977; 16/3/1977; 17/3/1977; 18/3/1977
    - May Chareu Su, 23/3/1976 (Reel 185, Frame 10)
    - May L'En, 10/12/1978 (Reel 79, Frame 20)
    - May Moeuy, N/A (Reel 70, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/2/1977; 16/2/1977; 16/2/1977; 1 section undated
    - May Nan, 11/11/1976 (Reel 81, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/1/1977; 24/12/1976; 20/12/1976; 17/12/1976; 3/1/1977
    - May Sakhan, N/A (Reel 70, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 8/12/1976; 3/1/1977; 30/12/1976; 8/12/1976; 23/11/1976; 10/11/1976; 11/11/1976; 9/11/1976; 29/10/1976; 25/10/1976; 19/10/1976; 30/11/1976; 26/11/1976
    - Me Sarun, 14/14/? 77 (Reel 74, Frame 26)
      Dates of Confessions: 20/1/1978; 25/2/1978
    - Meach Man, 25/1/1978 (Reel 80, Frame 31)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/1/1978
    - Meach Ol, N/A (Reel 79, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/11/1977; 18/11/1977; 3/1/1978
    - Meach Say, 10/10/1977 (Reel 72, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 7/1/1978(2); 23/9/1977; 30/11/1977
    - Meach Suon, 12/10/1976 (Reel 76, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/12/1976(2); 9/11/1976(2); 15/12/1976; 20/12/1976; 7/1/1977(2); 1 section undated
    - Meach Yom, N/A (Reel 74, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 10/1/1977
    - Meak, N/A (Reel 78, Frame 19)
      Dates of Confessions: 8/1976; 11/11/1976; 4/12/1976; 16/10/1976; 12/10/ 76; 18/10/1976; 24/10/1976; 10/11/1976; 1/11/1976; 7/11/1976
    - Meak Touch, 20/11/1977 (Reel 75, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/2//1978
    - Meal Ray, 3/2/1978 (Reel 78, Frame 3)
    - Mean Chang, 26/6/1976 (Reel 75, Frame 20)
    - Mean Choeun, 9/1976 (Reel 78, Frame 27)
      Dates of Confessions: 15/9/1976; 28/9/1976; 29/9/1976(2); 4/10/1976; 3/10/1976(3); 30/9/1976(2); 1/10/1976(2); 2/10/1976; 5 sections undated
    - Mean Moeus, 14/6/79 (Reel 76, Frame 15)
    - Mean Oeurn, N/A (Reel 74, Frame 23)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/10/1976
    - Mean Say, 21/4/1978 (Reel 77, Frame 19)
    - Mean Thon, N/A (Reel 71, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/9/1975
    - Mean Von, N/A (Reel 80, Frame 16)
      Dates of Confessions: 22/6/1977
    - Mean Yaun, 13/10/1977 (Reel 75, Frame 17)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/1/1978; 11/12/1977
    - Meas Bun Than, N/A (Reel 75, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/2/1977; 4/2/1977; 11/2/1977; 15/2/1977; 17/2/1977(2)
    - Meas Chandy, 19/3/1978 (Reel 71, Frame 11)
    - Meas Chhan, 28/8/1977 (Reel 78, Frame 8)
    - Meas Chhith, 15/4/1978 (Reel 71, Frame 18)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/5/1978; 12/5/1978; 3/6/1978
    - Meas Chhuon, N/A (Reel 71, Frame 12)